<resources>
    <string name="almost_done">Almost done!</string>
    <string name="already_spent">already spent</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="app_name">MYnance</string>
    <string name="apr">April</string>
    <string name="apr1">Apr</string>
    <string name="ask_later">Okay, we\'ll ask you again later.</string>
    <string name="aug">August</string>
    <string name="aug1">Aug</string>
    <string name="available_to_spend">Available to spend:</string>
    <string name="bi_annually">Twice a year (2 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="bi_monthly">Twice a month (24 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="bi_weekly">Every 2 weeks (26 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="budget">Budget</string>
    <string name="budget_1">The budget you create is for a year, so the total income and total expenses showing are calculated for a year based on your entries.</string>
    <string name="budget_2">Use the PLUS buttons to add income items or expense items.</string>
    <string name="budget_3">You make a budget for 2 reasons:</string>
    <string name="budget_4">1. To make sure you are not spending more money than you earn.</string>
    <string name="budget_5">2. To give you spending guidelines for optional items like gifts, entertainment, clothing, etc.</string>
    <string name="budget_6">MYnance will alert you if your budget does not balance (i.e. if you are spending more money than you earn).</string>
    <string name="budget_7">MYnance is a real-world budgeting app. We believe that tracking each expense category separately is too restrictive an approach and does not align with most peoples\' reality.</string>
    <string name="budget_8">Instead, the money needed to pay for expense categories identified by you as needs will be \'reserved\' in your bank account and the remainder will be \'available to spend\'.</string>
    <string name="budget_9">MYnance can help you to track your spending on optional items (see DAILY MONEY - WEEKLY LIMITS section).</string>
    <string name="budget_10">Payments made to DEBTS and SAVINGS will be added to your budget automatically and treated as needs, so that the money will be \'reserved\' in your bank account.</string>
    <string name="budget_11">You should adjust your budget any time a major change occurs (i.e. you get a raise at work or the amount of a payment changes).</string>
    <string name="budget_12">You should review and update your budget at least once a year.</string>
    <string name="budget_13">You can use the SPENDING REPORT as a guideline when updating your budget. Running a spending report for an entire year will show you how much you actually spent in each category.</string>
    <string name="budget_14">Updating your budget will not adjust your bank account balances retroactively. The app will simply adjust the percentage of future entries to \'reserve\' for needs in accordance with the changes made to the budget.</string>
    <string name="budget_does_not_balance">WARNING: Your budget doesn\'t balance. Please go to the BUDGET screen to fix it.</string>
    <string name="by">by</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cannot_delete_budget">You cannot delete this budget item, it is linked to DEBTS and/or SAVINGS items. You can enter $0 as the amount so it will have no effect on your budget.</string>
    <string name="cannot_delete_warning">You cannot delete this entry.</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="changes_saved">Your changes have been saved</string>
    <string name="check_boxes_below">Check the boxes below of the credit card purchases that you want to pay today.</string>
    <string name="check_box_prompt">Check box once payment made</string>
    <string name="check_box_starting_balance">(Check the box once you\'ve entered an amount below)</string>
    <string name="check_box_to_start">Check the box when you\'re ready to start!</string>
    <string name="choose_email">Choose an Email client</string>
    <string name="click_here_budget">click here to finish making your budget</string>
    <string name="click_here_debts">click here to enter your debts</string>
    <string name="click_here_savings">click here to enter your savings</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_1">Contact us, we\'d love to hear from you!</string>
    <string name="contact_us_2">Send us an email:</string>
    <string name="contact_us_3">or visit our website:</string>
    <string name="continue1">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_anyway">Continue anyway?</string>
    <string name="continue_warning">NOTE: Your account balances will not be affected until you pay this item in the \'Pay CC\' tab.</string>
    <string name="credit_card">Credit card</string>
    <string name="credit_card_1">Use this tab to record any purchases made against credit cards or lines of credit.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_2">For each purchase, you will select an expense item in your BUDGET, such as \'insurance\' or \'entertainment. You will also select which DEBTS item to map the purchase against.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_3">The DEBTS item\'s balance owing will be updated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_4">NOTE: Be careful about mapping a purchase to the same BUDGET and DEBTS item.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_5">It is possible to use a DEBTS item as the selected budget item. For example, if you took money from a credit card to pay down a line of credit.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_6">In that case, the amount of the payment would be added to the balance owing on the credit card and subtracted from the balance owing on the line of credit. If you mapped to the same item twice, the balance owing on the DEBTS item would not update correctly.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_7">MYnance wants to help you develop healthy spending habits. It will alert you if you are making purchases against your DEBTS items when you don\'t have the funds in your account to cover them.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_8">Although purchases entered in this tab will have no effect on your \'total\' and \'available to spend\' balances, you should still avoid accumulating consumer debt.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_9">Payments to your DEBTS items should be made in the PAY CC tab. Your \'total\' and \'available to spend\' balances will change when payments are made in the PAY CC tab and the DEBTS item\'s balance owing will be updated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_10">However, purchases recorded in this tab will show up in your SPENDING REPORT as having been spent on the date the entry was made.</string>
    <string name="current_balance">Current balance:</string>
    <string name="daily_money">Daily Money</string>
    <string name="daily_money_1">\'Total in Account\' is the total amount of money in your bank account. A percentage of this money is reserved for paying \'needs\', as identified by you in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_2">\'Available to Spend\' is the amount of money that you can spend on \'optional\' expenses, as identified by you in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="debt">Debt</string>
    <string name="debts">Debts</string>
    <string name="debts_1">MYnance will calculate the date that a debt will be paid off, based on your entries.</string>
    <string name="debts_2">You can use the DEBTS screen to see the effects of changing a loan or credit card payment.</string>
    <string name="debts_3">When adding or updating a debt item, the payment amount you enter will automatically be added to your budget and treated as a need, so the money will be reserved in your bank account.</string>
    <string name="debts_4">Each credit card you own must be set up in the DEBTS screen if you want to record purchases against them in the DAILY MONEY - CREDIT CARD tab.</string>
    <string name="debts_5">MYnance will help you keep your credit card balances at zero in the DAILY MONEY - PAY CC tab.</string>
    <string name="debts_6">If you take a cash advance off a DEBTS item, you can enter the transaction in the DAILY MONEY - MONEY IN tab. You bank account balances will be adjusted accordingly. DON\'T FORGET that only a percentage of that deposit will be \'available to spend\'.</string>
    <string name="debts_7">If you take frequent cash advances off DEBTS items, you should adjust your BUDGET to reflect this income.</string>
    <string name="debts_8">NOTE: If you create an INCOME from a DEBT, the \'debt-free\' date for it will be adjusted accordingly. This change will be reflected in the DEBTS screen.</string>
    <string name="debts_9">Purchases against and payments to your debts in the DAILY MONEY tabs will be automatically added or subtracted to the balances owing in the DEBTS screen.</string>
    <string name="debt_free_by">Debt-free by</string>
    <string name="debt_paid">Debt paid!</string>
    <string name="debt_saved">This debt has been saved to your BUDGET</string>
    <string name="debt_will">Will be paid by </string>
    <string name="dec">December</string>
    <string name="dec1">Dec</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete this item</string>
    <string name="done">DONE</string>
    <string name="done_budget">done entering budget</string>
    <string name="done_debts">done entering debts</string>
    <string name="done_savings">done entering savings</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit this item</string>
    <string name="edit_budget_message">You can edit this list by clicking BUDGET on the menu</string>
    <string name="edit_debts_message">You can edit this list by clicking DEBTS on the menu</string>
    <string name="edit_savings_message">You can edit this list by clicking SAVINGS on the menu</string>
    <string name="email_address" translatable="false">gotchasomething.ca@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="email_question">Will you please let us know what we need to change to make it better?</string>
    <string name="email_warning">There are no email clients installed</string>
    <string name="empty_money_out">Use this tab to record all the transactions when money leaves your bank account.</string>
    <string name="enjoying_question">Are you enjoying using this app?</string>
    <string name="enter">enter</string>
    <string name="enter_debt_amount">How much do you owe?</string>
    <string name="enter_debts">Enter debts</string>
    <string name="enter_exp_cat">Enter an expense category</string>
    <string name="enter_income_cat">Enter an income category</string>
    <string name="enter_int_frequency">How often is the interest compounded?</string>
    <string name="enter_limit">What is the maximum you could borrow (or the starting amount of the loan)?</string>
    <string name="enter_payments">How much are your payments?</string>
    <string name="enter_rate">What is the interest rate being charged?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings">Enter savings</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_amount">What is the current balance?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_cat">What are you saving for?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_goal">What is the total amount you want to save?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_payments">How much are you contributing?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_rate">What is the annual interest rate being earned?</string>
    <string name="expenses">Expenses:</string>
    <string name="feb">February</string>
    <string name="feb1">Feb</string>
    <string name="finish_budget">Finish budget</string>
    <string name="get_started">Let\'s get started!</string>
    <string name="goal_achieved">Goal achieved!</string>
    <string name="goal_never">There is no money here.</string>
    <string name="goal_will">Will be saved by </string>
    <string name="google_play_url" translatable="false">market://details?id=ca.gotchasomething.mynance</string>
    <string name="go_to_daily_money">Go to \'Daily Money\' to make income and spending entries, to track your credit card transactions, and to watch your weekly spending limits</string>
    <string name="go_to_daily_money_2">Go to DAILY MONEY to record your spending in the MONEY OUT tab.</string>
    <string name="go_to_help">Go to \'Help\' if you need more guidance</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="hide">hide</string>
    <string name="how_often">How often?</string>
    <string name="income">Income:</string>
    <string name="income_available">Income still available for budgeting:</string>
    <string name="jan">January</string>
    <string name="jan1">Jan</string>
    <string name="jul">July</string>
    <string name="jul1">Jul</string>
    <string name="jun">June</string>
    <string name="jun1">Jun</string>
    <string name="left_this_week">left this week</string>
    <string name="limit_warning">Making this purchase will put this DEBTS item over its limit.</string>
    <string name="logo" translatable="false">Logo</string>
    <string name="manage_money">Now you can manage your money in just a few minutes a day!</string>
    <string name="mar">March</string>
    <string name="mar1">Mar</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="may1">May</string>
    <string name="money_in">Money In</string>
    <string name="money_in_1">Use this tab to record any money that goes into your bank account.</string>
    <string name="money_in_2">Each entry will map to an income item in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="money_in_3">When you created your budget, you identified which expense items were for needs and which were for optional spending.</string>
    <string name="money_in_4">The appropriate percentage of each MONEY IN entry will be reserved for needs according to these BUDGET entries. The remainder will be allotted to the \'available to spend\' amount.</string>
    <string name="money_out">Money Out</string>
    <string name="money_out_1">Use this tab to record any CASH that comes out of your bank account, either as a cheque, cash withdrawal, or debit card purchase.</string>
    <string name="money_out_2">NOTE: It is up to you whether you create \'cash withdrawal\' as an expense item in your budget and track withdrawals as one item or whether you account for cash withdrawals as a breakdown of what the money was used for (i.e. $20 withdrawal entered as $10 towards \'entertainment\' and $10 towards \'miscellaneous\').</string>
    <string name="money_out_3">JUST BE SURE that each cash withdrawal is only entered once in MONEY OUT, otherwise too much money will be taken out of your \'total\' and \'available to spend\' balances.</string>
    <string name="money_out_4">Purchases made on a credit card must be entered in the CREDIT CARD tab so that the credit card\'s DEBTS record will be updated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="money_out_5">You can view a summary of your MONEY OUT items in the SPENDING REPORT screen.</string>
    <string name="money_out_cc_prompt">Use this tab to record all the transactions when you use your credit cards.</string>
    <string name="monthly">Once a month (12 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="mynance_will_show_you">MYnance will show you how much money in your bank account is actually available to spend at any given time</string>
    <string name="my_preference" translatable="false">ca.gotchasomething.ca.MyPref</string>
    <string name="my_preference_key" translatable="false">ca.gotchasomething.ca.MyPrefKey</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="name_debt">Name this debt</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="needs">This expense is for needs (i.e. food, rent, insurance, etc)</string>
    <string name="next_button">next</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="no_blanks_warning">You cannot leave blank fields</string>
    <string name="no_debt_item_warning">You must create a DEBT item to charge this purchase against.</string>
    <string name="no_debts_message">You have no outstanding credit card purchases!</string>
    <string name="no_debts_yet">You haven\'t entered any debts yet.</string>
    <string name="no_debt_warning">NOTE: There must be a DEBT item created for each credit card.</string>
    <string name="no_exp_warning">You must create expense items in your BUDGET to spend against</string>
    <string name="no_limit_warning">You must enter a maximum debt limit</string>
    <string name="no_savings">You haven\'t entered any savings yet.</string>
    <string name="no_spending_during_period">There was no spending during that period.</string>
    <string name="no_spending_yet">You haven\'t entered any spending yet.</string>
    <string name="not_enough_credit_warning">There is not enough credit available on this DEBTS item to make this deposit. You will be putting the debt over its limit.</string>
    <string name="not_enough_savings_warning">There is not enough in this SAVINGS item to make this deposit. You will be putting the savings balance into the negative.</string>
    <string name="not_now">not now</string>
    <string name="not_sure_yet">not sure yet</string>
    <string name="nov">November</string>
    <string name="nov1">Nov</string>
    <string name="oct">October</string>
    <string name="oct1">Oct</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="oops">Oops, you are spending more than you make!</string>
    <string name="optional">This expense is optional (i.e. entertainment, gifts, clothing, etc)</string>
    <string name="outstanding_cc_purchases">Outstanding credit card purchases</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="pay_cc">Pay cc</string>
    <string name="pay_cc_1">MYnance is a great tool to help you make sure you avoid consumer debt. Use this tab to manage money owing on DEBTS items resulting from purchases.</string>
    <string name="pay_cc_2">Enter any purchases you make on credit cards or lines of credit in the CREDIT CARD tab and make frequent payments to them using the PAY CC tab.</string>
    <string name="pay_cc_3">If you want to make additional payments to your DEBTS items that don\'t map to particular purchases, you can enter those transactions in the DAILY MONEY - MONEY OUT tab.</string>
    <string name="pay_cc_4">MYnance will alert you if you are trying to make a payment when you don\'t have the funds available in your \'total\' or \'available to spend\' balances.</string>
    <string name="pay_this_amount">Pay this amount to your credit card:</string>
    <string name="payment_not_possible_A">You don\'t have enough money in your account to make this purchase. You will put your balance into the negative.</string>
    <string name="payment_not_possible_B">You don\'t have enough spending money left in your account to make this purchase. You will be spending money that is reserved for other expenses.</string>
    <string name="plus_button_debts">Press the PLUS button above to add a debt.</string>
    <string name="plus_button_savings">Press the PLUS button above to add savings.</string>
    <string name="rate_it_question">Will you please take a moment to rate it?</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">Rate this app</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="savings">Savings</string>
    <string name="savings_1">MYnance will calculate the date that a savings goal will be met, based on your entries.</string>
    <string name="savings_2">You can use the SAVINGS screen to make a savings plan.</string>
    <string name="savings_3">When adding or updating a savings item, the contribution amount that you enter will automatically be added to your budget and treated as a need, so the money will be reserved in your bank account.</string>
    <string name="savings_4">If you make a withdrawal from a SAVINGS item, this transaction can be entered in the DAILY MONEY - MONEY IN tab. Your bank account balances will be adjusted accordingly. DON\'T FORGET that only a percentage of the deposit will be \'available for spending\'.</string>
    <string name="savings_5">If you make frequent withdrawals from SAVINGS items, you should adjust your BUDGET to reflect this income.</string>
    <string name="savings_6">NOTE: If you create an INCOME from a SAVINGS item, the amount of the contributions to it will be adjusted accordingly, as will the \'goal achieved\' date for it. These changes will be reflected in the SAVINGS screen.</string>
    <string name="savings_7">Payments towards and withdrawals from your savings items in the DAILY MONEY tabs will be automatically added to or subtracted from the balances in the SAVINGS screen.</string>
    <string name="savings_saved">This savings info has been saved to your BUDGET</string>
    <string name="sep">September</string>
    <string name="sep1">Sep</string>
    <string name="set_up">Set Up</string>
    <string name="set_up_1">The automatic set up process walked you through setting up your debts, savings, and budget.</string>
    <string name="set_up_2">All of these items can be changed manually by using the MENU to access their screens.</string>
    <string name="set_up_3">You also entered a starting balance for your bank account. This amount can be changed by clicking on the pencil icon next to it in the DAILY MONEY - MONEY IN tab.</string>
    <string name="set_up_4">You can adjust the amount in your bank account by making entries in the DAILY MONEY screen.</string>
    <string name="show">show</string>
    <string name="show_report">show report</string>
    <string name="simple_date_format" translatable="false">dd-MMM-yyyy</string>
    <string name="skip_button">skip intro</string>
    <string name="slide1Description">Manage your money and keep on top of your debt in just a few steps</string>
    <string name="slide1Title">Welcome to MYnance!</string>
    <string name="slide2Description">Simply follow along with the guided set up process</string>
    <string name="slide2Title">Step 1:</string>
    <string name="slide3Description">Go to \'Daily Money\' to make income and spending entries, track your credit card transactions, and watch your weekly spending limits</string>
    <string name="slide3Title">Step 2:</string>
    <string name="slide4Title">MYnance will let you know how much money in your bank account is actually available for spending at any given time</string>
    <string name="slide5Title">MYnance will help you keep on top of your credit card spending so you avoid getting into consumer debt</string>
    <string name="slide6Title">Visit the \'Help\' section if you need more guidance</string>
    <string name="spending_report">Spending Report</string>
    <string name="spending_report_1">MYnance will show you your spending in each expense category of your budget by month or for the year to date.</string>
    <string name="spending_report_2">Simply use the pull-down menus to choose the period of time that you\'d like to see.</string>
    <string name="spending_report_3">When updating your budget, you can use the year to date spending report to see what your actual spending was in each category and use those numbers as the new budget amounts.</string>
    <string name="start_button">Got it!</string>
    <string name="starting_balance">Starting Balance</string>
    <string name="starting_balance_amount">How much money is in your bank account today?</string>
    <string name="sure">sure!</string>
    <string name="too_far">Too far in the future</string>
    <string name="total_expenses">Total Expenses:</string>
    <string name="total_in_account">Total in account:</string>
    <string name="total_income">Total Income:</string>
    <string name="total_owing">Total Owing:</string>
    <string name="total_saved">Total Saved:</string>
    <string name="update">update</string>
    <string name="website" translatable="false">www.gotchasomething.ca</string>
    <string name="weekly">Weekly (52 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits">Weekly Limits</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_1">When you create expense items in your BUDGET and identify them as \'optional\', you will be given the choice whether or not to manage their weekly spending limits.</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_2">You can change this setting for any expense item at any time in the BUDGET screen by clicking on the pencil icon next to the item.</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_3">MYnance will break the yearly amount for the item down to a weekly limit and track how much is left each week to spend on the item.</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_details">Mark budget expense items as \'optional\' and you will then be asked whether or not you would like to track their spending on a weekly basis.</string>
    <string name="weekly_limit_exceeded">WEEKLY LIMIT EXCEEDED</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_prompt">Weekly limits are set up in the BUDGET screen.</string>
    <string name="weekly_no">No: This is an occasional expense and I don\'t need weekly guidance</string>
    <string name="weekly_yes">Yes: I spend on this frequently and would like to be reminded of my limits</string>
    <string name="weekly_yes_or_no">Do you want this category added to the WEEKLY LIMITS tab to help you stay within your spending limits?</string>
    <string name="which_debt">On which DEBT?</string>
    <string name="yearly">Once a year (1 time/yr)</string>
    <string name="year_to_date">Entire year to date</string>
    <string name="year_to_date1">all</string>
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
</resources>
