<resources>
    <string name="step_1">Step 1:</string>
    <string name="a_text1">Manage your money and keep on top of your debt in just a few steps</string>
    <string name="a_text2">Simply follow along with the guided set up process</string>
    <string name="a_text3">Go to the Home Page to make income and spending entries, track your credit card transactions, and watch your weekly spending limits</string>
    <string name="a_text4">MYnance will let you know how much money in your bank account is actually available for spending at any given time</string>
    <string name="a_text5">MYnance will help you keep on top of your credit card spending so you avoid getting into consumer debt</string>
    <string name="a_text6">Visit the \'Help\' section if you need more guidance</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="add_item">Click here to add another item</string>
    <string name="adjust_income">adjust income</string>
    <string name="adjust_expenses">adjust expenses</string>
    <string name="already_spent">already spent</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="analysis_adjustments">Analysis and adjustments (if necessary)</string>
    <string name="another_bill">add another bill</string>
    <string name="another_debt">add another debt</string>
    <string name="another_income">add another income category</string>
    <string name="another_savings">add another savings</string>
    <string name="app_name">MYnance</string>
    <string name="apr">April</string>
    <string name="ask_later">Okay, we\'ll ask you again later.</string>
    <string name="aug">August</string>
    <string name="available_to_spend">Available to spend:</string>

    <string name="lets_get_real">Let\'s get real!</string>
    <string name="b2_text1">MYnance is a real-world app, so no tedious budgeting here. MYnance will help you make sure you\'re not over-spending or racking up debt.</string>
    <string name="b2_text2">To get started, you\'ll enter some quick estimates, but as you use the app, MYnance will update those numbers with actual data for more accuracy.</string>
    <string name="b2_text3">MYnance will use that info to reserve money in your main bank account to pay bills and let you know how much is left for you to spend on other things.</string>
    <string name="b2_text4">First, set up each of your sources of income separately in the following screen.</string>
    <string name="b3_text1">You\'ll tell us about your bills next. Bills are payments you regularly make.</string>
    <string name="b3_text3">Bills DO include items that are necessary living expenses (groceries, rent, insurance, etc.) and obligations (memberships, yearly vehicle registration costs, etc.).</string>
    <string name="b3_text4">Bills DO NOT include credit cards or savings. You\'ll set those up separately in another screen.</string>
    <string name="b3_text5">Bills also DO NOT include optional expenses or spending (entertainment, travel, clothing, gifts, etc.).</string>
    <string name="b3_text6">For simplicity, add up amounts for bills that are similar and enter them as one bill. For example, if you pay for swimming lessons and martial arts, enter them as one bill called \'lessons\' or \'kids activities\'.</string>
    <string name="do_include">DO include:</string>
    <string name="necessary_expenses">necessary living expenses</string>
    <string name="regular_payments">regular service payments</string>
    <string name="memberships">memberships/obligations</string>
    <string name="do_not_include">DO NOT include:</string>
    <string name="debts_loans">debts/loans</string>
    <string name="credit_vehicles">credit cards/lines of credit</string>
    <string name="mortgages">mortgages</string>
    <string name="savings_investments">savings/investments</string>
    <string name="unnecessary_spending">unnecessary spending</string>
    <string name="b4_text1">MYnance will help you make a debt repayment plan by calculating debt-free dates for each of your credit cards and lines of credit.</string>
    <string name="b4_text2">Set up each of your credit cards and lines of credit separately, even if you don\'t usually use them or owe any money on them.</string>
    <string name="b4_text3">Set up each of your other debts separately too, including mortgages and personal loans.</string>
    <string name="b5_text1">Savings is any money that you set aside for any reason, whether it\'s short-term (to buy something in particular) or long-term (in case of emergency, for retirement, or for investment).</string>
    <string name="b5_text2">MYnance will help you make a savings plan by calculating the dates that you will achieve your savings goals.</string>
    <string name="thanks">Perfects, thanks!</string>
    <string name="b6_text1">Now that you\'ve entered all that info, MYnance can analyze your spending and flag any issues.</string>
    <string name="b6_text2">You\'ll have an opportunity to make adjustments, if necessary.</string>
    <string name="spending_analysis">Spending Analysis</string>
    <string name="analysis_explanation_2">Ideally, shouldn\'t be using more than 80% of your income for living expenses.</string>
    <string name="anaresult">anaResult</string>
    <string name="ana_res_prt_1">You\'re currently spending about</string>
    <string name="ana_res_part_2">of your income on living expenses.</string>
    <string name="recommended_amt">Congratulations! You\'re spending is right where it should be.</string>
    <string name="higher_than_recommended">Oh oh, you\'re spending is a little higher than it should be.</string>
    <string name="too_high">Warning: You\'re spending is too high!</string>
    <string name="no_adj_nec">No adjustments necessary!</string>
    <string name="may_adj">You may want to make adjustments in one of the areas below.</string>
    <string name="should_adj">You should try to make adjustments in one of the areas below.</string>
    <string name="almost_done">Almost done!</string>
    <string name="what_mynance_does">MYnance will:</string>
    <string name="b7_text1">Let you know how much of your money is available for unnecessary spending.</string>
    <string name="b7_text2">Organize your credit card purchases so you can pay them off quickly and avoid interest charges.</string>
    <string name="b7_text3">Watch your weekly spending in areas identified by you.</string>
    <string name="b7_text4">You don\'t have to use this feature to use the app, but you can identify existing or create new spending categories where you\'d like MYnance to keep an eye on your spending habits.</string>
    <string name="one_more_thing">Just one more thing&#8230;</string>
    <string name="one_more_thing_2">&#8230;and you\'re ready to go!</string>
    <string name="b8_text1">Remember, MYnance is completely secure because it\'s not linked to any outside websites or databases.</string>
    <string name="b8_text2">All your information is stored safely on your own device.</string>
    <string name="b8_text3">And you don\'t need to enter any bank account, credit card numbers, or PINs into the app.</string>
    <string name="b8_text4">You do need to let the app know how much money is in your main bank account today, so it can tell you how much of that money you can spend! Enter it below:</string>

    <string name="bi_annually">Twice a year (2 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="bill_amount">What is the usual amount of this bill?</string>
    <string name="bill_frequency">How often do you pay this bill?</string>
    <string name="bills">Regular Bills:</string>
    <string name="bi_monthly">Twice a month (24 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="bi_weekly">Every 2 weeks (26 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="budget">Budget</string>
    <string name="budget_1">When you created DEBTS or SAVINGS accounts, MYnance automatically creates linked income and expenses categories in your BUDGET. In order to preserve linked data properly, you can only delete these items by deleting the parent accounts in either DEBTS or SAVINGS.</string>
    <string name="budget_2">Simply use the PLUS buttons to add income categories (all your sources of incoming money) and expenses categories (all the things you spend your money on).</string>
    <string name="budget_3">You make a budget for 2 reasons:</string>
    <string name="budget_4">1. To make sure you are not spending more money than you earn.</string>
    <string name="budget_5">2. To give you spending guidelines for optional items like gifts, entertainment, clothing, etc.</string>
    <string name="budget_6">MYnance will alert you if your budget does not balance (i.e. if you are spending more money than you earn).</string>
    <string name="budget_7">A realistic budget captures all the major areas of your spending, without getting too bogged down in details.</string>
    <string name="budget_8">For example, you could create a category for \"kids\' lessons\", as opposed to 3 separate categories for \"Tommy\'s hockey\", \"Trina\'s dance\", and \"swimming lessons\".</string>
    <string name="budget_9">\"Optional\" expenses categories are not necessary in order to use this app, however including them in your BUDGET will give you valuable spending guidelines in your daily life. For example, you will learn how often you can afford to spend money on entertainment or how much money you can afford to spend on gifts.</string>
    <string name="budget_11">You should also adjust your budget any time a major change occurs (i.e. you get a raise at work or the amount of a payment changes).</string>
    <string name="budget_12">You should review and update your budget at least once a year.</string>
    <string name="budget_13">You can use the SPENDING REPORT as a guideline when updating your budget. Running a spending report for an entire year will show you how much you actually spent in each category.</string>
    <string name="budget_14">Updating your budget will not adjust your bank account balances retroactively. The app will simply adjust the percentage of future entries to \'reserve\' for needs in accordance with the changes made to the budget.</string>
    <string name="budget_does_not_balance">WARNING: You are spending more than you earn. Please CLICK HERE to fix it.</string>
    <string name="budget_q1">Why can\'t I delete certain income or expenses categories?</string>
    <string name="budget_q2">I need guidance to make a budget.</string>
    <string name="budget_q3">How often should I make changes to my budget?</string>
    <string name="budget_report_exp">Budget Report - Expenses</string>
    <string name="budget_report_inc">Budget Report - Income</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cannot_delete_budget">You can\'t delete this item, it\'s linked to a DEBT or SAVINGS item. You can enter $0 as its amount so no money will be reserved for it.</string>
    <string name="cash_debit_transactions">Cash/Debit Transactions:</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="change_default">Did you want to change the default amount for this category?</string>
    <string name="changes_saved">Your changes have been saved</string>
    <string name="check_boxes_below">Check the boxes below of the credit card purchases that you want to pay today.</string>
    <string name="check_box_prompt">Check box once payments made</string>
    <string name="check_box_starting_balance">(Check the box once you\'ve entered an amount below)</string>
    <string name="check_box_to_start">Check the box when you\'re ready to start.</string>
    <string name="choose_email">Choose an Email client</string>
    <string name="choose_cc">Choose a credit card or create a new one</string>
    <string name="choose_or_create">Choose categories below or create a new one.</string>
    <string name="click_here_analysis">Click here to get an analysis of your spending</string>
    <string name="click_here_begin">Click here to begin</string>
    <string name="click_here_budget">click here to finish making your budget</string>
    <string name="click_here_debts">click here to enter your debts</string>
    <string name="click_here_debts2">Click here to enter a new debts item</string>
    <string name="click_here_next">Click here next</string>
    <string name="click_here_savings">click here to enter your savings</string>
    <string name="click_here_savings2">Click here to add a new savings item</string>
    <string name="click_here_weekly">Click here to set up weekly spending limits.</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_1">Contact us, we\'d love to hear from you!</string>
    <string name="contact_us_2">Send us an email:</string>
    <string name="contact_us_3">or visit our website:</string>
    <string name="continue1">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_anyway">Continue anyway?</string>
    <string name="continue_warning">NOTE: Your account balances will not be affected until you pay this item in the \'Pay CC\' tab.</string>
    <string name="create">create</string>
    <string name="create_category">create a new category</string>
    <string name="create_cc">Create a new credit card</string>
    <string name="create_new_category">or create new category</string>
    <string name="credit_card">Credit card</string>
    <string name="credit_card_purchases">Credit card purchases</string>
    <string name="credit_card_purchases_2">Credit card purchases:</string>
    <string name="current_balance">Current balance:</string>
    <string name="daily_money">Daily Money</string>
    <string name="daily_money_1">\"Total in Account\" is the total amount of money in your bank account. A percentage of this money is reserved for paying \"needs\", as identified by you in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_2">\"Available to Spend\" is the amount of money that you can spend on \"optional\" expenses, as identified by you in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_3">This app is smart! When you overspend, it won\'t make money \"Available to Spend\" until you\'ve caught up on having enough money reserved for paying the \"needs\" you\'ve identified in your BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_4">The app will reserve the percentage of any money you put into your bank account that you identified in your BUDGET as being needed to pay for \"needs\". Only the balance of your income will be \"Available to Spend\".</string>
    <string name="daily_money_5">You can transfer money between any DEBTS and/or SAVINGS accounts in the TRANSFER FUNDS screen.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_6">How you handle cash withdrawals is a personal choice.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_6A">You can create a \"cash withdrawal\" expenses category in your BUDGET and record the transaction once against it, or you can choose to record where every dollar of the cash withdrawal was spent against several expenses categories.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_6B">MYnance believes the 2nd method will become tedious and is an unrealistic way to manage your money. It should suffice to record the cash withdrawal as a whole. You can use the SPENDING REPORT to identify if frequent cash withdrawals are a problem area for you.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_7">MYnance believes strongly in avoiding consumer debt on credit cards. The DAILY MONEY - PAY CC tab is built specifically for this purpose.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_7A">Using this tab once a week or more to make frequent payments to your credit card will ensure that you never pay interest on those purchases, but you will still earn the rewards that your credit card offers! </string>
    <string name="daily_money_7B">You can also make additional payments that don\'t map to specific purchases by using the DAILY MONEY - MONEY OUT tab or use the TRANSFER FUNDS screen to pay your credit card from another DEBTS or SAVINGS account.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_8">MYnance believes that blind spending on credit cards leads to consumer debt. That is why we will alert you if you don\'t have the funds to cover your credit card purchases.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_9">When you identify an expense category in your BUDGET as \"optional\", the app will ask you if you\'d like to track your spending on a weekly basis. If yes, you can use the DAILY MONEY - WEEKLY LIMITS tab to see how much has been spent between Monday and Sunday of this week against that category.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_10">Once you\'ve made a payment to a credit card against a particular purchase, that purchase can no longer be deleted.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_11">Only credit card purchases will appear in the PAY CC tab. Any transaction that is a transfer of funds to another DEBTS account or a SAVINGS account can be paid back by using the DAILY MONEY - MONEY OUT tab or the TRANSFER FUNDS screen.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q1">What does \"Total in Account\" mean?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q2">What does \"Available to Spend\" mean?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q3">I put money into my account, but the \"Available to Spend\" amount is still zero.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q4">It seems like the wrong amount is going into the \"Available to Spend\" amount.</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q5">The DAILY MONEY - MONEY IN tab only allows me to put money into my bank account. Where do I go to put money into my other accounts?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q6">When I take a cash withdrawal from my bank account, how can I record what I spend the money on?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q7">What is the difference between using the DAILY MONEY - PAY CC tab or the DAILY MONEY - MONEY OUT tab to record a payment to my credit card?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q8">Why does MYnance give me spending warnings when I\'m using my credit card?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q9">What are weekly limits and how can I set them up?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q10">Why am I unable to delete some of the items in the DAILY MONEY - CREDIT CARD tab?</string>
    <string name="daily_money_q11">Why don\'t all my credit card transactions appear in the PAY CC tab?</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="debt">Debt</string>
    <string name="debts">Debts</string>
    <string name="debts_1">Enter each of your credit cards, loans, mortgages, lines of credit or other outstanding debts as a separate DEBTS account. They will automatically be added to your BUDGET as \"needs\" and the date that the debt will be paid off will be calculated for you.</string>
    <string name="debts_2">The app has calculated that the debt will not be paid off in a reasonable amount of time. Either the interest is too high or the payments are too low or too infrequent.</string>
    <string name="debts_3">Simply click on the pencil icon next to the account in the DEBTS screen and enter the new interest rate. A new debt-free date will calculated.</string>
    <string name="debts_4">When you created the DEBTS account, a linked income category was created for you in your BUDGET. Simply click on the pencil icon next to it on the BUDGET screen and enter the amount of income that you plan on taking from the DEBTS account. A new debt-free date will be calculated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="debts_5">Create an expenses category in your BUDGET called \"interest\" (or something similar). Use the DAILY MONEY - CREDIT CARD tab to create entries against that category (in the 1st pull-down menu), charged against the DEBTS account (in the 2nd pull-down menu).</string>
    <string name="debts_q1">I need guidance to enter debts accounts.</string>
    <string name="debts_q2">Why does the date come up as \"Too far in the future\"?</string>
    <string name="debts_q3">What if the interest rate changes on my DEBTS account?</string>
    <string name="debts_q4">I frequently take cash advances off a DEBTS account, how should I get the app to handle this?</string>
    <string name="debts_q5">How can I record the interest I get charged on my DEBTS accounts?</string>
    <string name="debt_free_by">Debt-free by</string>
    <string name="debt_paid">Debt paid!</string>
    <string name="debt_saved">This debt has been saved to your BUDGET</string>
    <string name="debt_will">Will be paid by </string>
    <string name="dec">December</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete this item</string>
    <string name="delete_debt_warning">Warning: When you delete this item, the corresponding income and expense categories will also be deleted from your BUDGET</string>
    <string name="deposit">Deposited</string>
    <string name="deposits">Deposits</string>
    <string name="done">DONE</string>
    <string name="done_bills">done entering bills</string>
    <string name="done_budget">done entering budget</string>
    <string name="done_debts">done entering debts</string>
    <string name="done_entering_items">Done entering items</string>
    <string name="done_income_categories">Done entering income categories</string>
    <string name="done_money_in">Done entering deposits</string>
    <string name="done_savings">done entering savings</string>
    <string name="done_set_up">Congratulations! You\'re done setting MYnance up!</string>
    <string name="done_transfers">Done Transfers</string>
    <string name="done_weekly_limits">Weekly limits set up</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit this item</string>
    <string name="edit_budget_message">You can edit this list by clicking BUDGET on the menu</string>
    <string name="edit_debts_message">You can edit this list by clicking DEBTS on the menu</string>
    <string name="edit_savings_message">You can edit this list by clicking SAVINGS on the menu</string>
    <string name="email_address" translatable="false">gotchasomething.ca@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="email_question">Will you please let us know what we need to change to make it better?</string>
    <string name="email_warning">There are no email clients installed</string>
    <string name="empty_budget">After you have clicked the \'Done Entering Budget\' button, you will still be able to edit these items by using the menu to access the BUDGET screen.</string>
    <string name="empty_debts_3">After you have clicked the \'Done Entering Debts\' button, you will still be able to edit these items by using the menu to access the DEBTS screen.</string>
    <string name="empty_money_out">Use this tab to record all the transactions when money leaves your bank account.</string>
    <string name="empty_savings_3">After you have clicked the \'Done Entering Savings\' button, you will still be able to edit these items by using the menu to access the SAVINGS screen.</string>
    <string name="enjoying_question">Are you enjoying using this app?</string>
    <string name="enter">enter</string>
    <string name="enter_balance">Enter account starting balance.</string>
    <string name="enter_bills">Enter bills</string>
    <string name="enter_debt_amount">How much do you owe?</string>
    <string name="enter_debts">Enter credit cards/lines of credit</string>
    <string name="enter_exp_cat">Enter an expense category</string>
    <string name="enter_income">Enter income</string>
    <string name="enter_income_cat">Enter an income category</string>
    <string name="enter_int_frequency">How often is the interest compounded?</string>
    <string name="enter_limit">What is the credit limit?</string>
    <string name="enter_new_amt">Or enter another amount</string>
    <string name="enter_payments">How much do you usually pay each month?</string>
    <string name="enter_rate">What is the interest rate being charged?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings">Enter savings</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_amount">How much do you already have saved for this?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_cat">What are you saving for?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_goal">What is the total amount you want to save?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_payments">How much money do you usually put towards this every month?</string>
    <string name="enter_savings_rate">What is the annual interest rate being earned (if any)?</string>
    <string name="expense_categories">Expense Categories:</string>
    <string name="expenses">Expenses</string>
    <string name="feb">February</string>
    <string name="finish_budget">Finish budget</string>
    <string name="first_thing_first">First thing\'s first&#8230;</string>
    <string name="from">from</string>
    <string name="get_started">Let\'s get started!</string>
    <string name="goal_achieved">Goal achieved!</string>
    <string name="goal_will">Will be saved by </string>
    <string name="google_play_url" translatable="false">market://details?id=ca.gotchasomething.mynance</string>
    <string name="go_to_daily_money">Go to \'Daily Money\' to make income and spending entries, to track your credit card transactions, and to watch your weekly spending limits</string>
    <string name="go_to_daily_money_2">Go to DAILY MONEY to record your spending in the MONEY OUT tab.</string>
    <string name="go_to_daily_money_3">Go to DAILY MONEY to record your income in the MONEY IN tab and your spending in the MONEY OUT tab.</string>
    <string name="go_to_help">Go to \'Help\' if you need more guidance</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_instructions">Choose a topic and then click on a question to see its answer.</string>
    <string name="hide">hide</string>
    <string name="hide_list">hide list</string>
    <string name="how_often">How often?</string>
    <string name="income">Income</string>
    <string name="income_available">Money not reserved for living expenses:</string>
    <string name="income_categories">Income Categories:</string>
    <string name="in_main_account">main account</string>
    <string name="jan">January</string>
    <string name="jul">July</string>
    <string name="jun">June</string>
    <string name="left_this_week">left this week</string>
    <string name="limit_warning">Making this purchase will put this DEBTS item over its limit.</string>
    <string name="logo" translatable="false">Logo</string>
    <string name="make_no_adjustments">done adjustments</string>
    <string name="manage_money">Now you can manage your money in just a few minutes a day!</string>
    <string name="mar">March</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="money_in">Money In</string>
    <string name="money_out">Money Out</string>
    <string name="money_out_cc_prompt">Use this tab to record all the transactions when you use your credit cards.</string>
    <string name="mon_in_debts_warn">Making this deposit will put the DEBTS item over its limit.</string>
    <string name="mon_in_sav_warn">Making this deposit will put the SAVINGS item\'s balance into the negative.</string>
    <string name="monthly">Once a month (12 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="mynance_will_show_you">MYnance will show you how much money in your bank account is actually available to spend at any given time</string>
    <string name="my_preference" translatable="false">ca.gotchasomething.ca.MyPref</string>
    <string name="my_preference_key" translatable="false">ca.gotchasomething.ca.MyPrefKey</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="name_bill">Name this bill</string>
    <string name="name_debt">Name this card or line of credit</string>
    <string name="name_this_category">Name this category</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="need_help">Click here if you need more help with this step.</string>
    <string name="need_help2">Just click on \"Done Entering Debts\" and visit the HELP section once you\'re done with the set up process. You can get the information you need there and finish this later.</string>
    <string name="need_help3">Just click on \"Done Entering Savings\" and visit the HELP section once you\'re done with the set up process. You can get the information you need there and finish this later.</string>
    <string name="need_help4">Just click on \"Done Entering Budget\" and visit the HELP section once you\'re done with the set up process. You can get the information you need there and finish this later.</string>
    <string name="needs">This expense is for needs (i.e. food, rent, insurance, etc)</string>
    <string name="next_button">next</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="no_amount_warning">You must enter an amount to transfer.</string>
    <string name="no_blanks_warning">You cannot leave blank fields</string>
    <string name="no_debt_item_warning">You must create a DEBT item to charge this purchase against.</string>
    <string name="no_debts_message">You have no outstanding credit card purchases!</string>
    <string name="no_debts_yet">You haven\'t entered any debts yet.</string>
    <string name="no_debt_warning">NOTE: There must be a DEBT item created for each credit card.</string>
    <string name="no_entries_yet">You haven\'t made any entries yet.</string>
    <string name="no_exp_warning">You must create expense items in your BUDGET to spend against</string>
    <string name="no_from_item_warning">You must choose an account to make the transfer from.</string>
    <string name="no_inc_warning">You must create income categories in the \'SPENDING VS. EARNINGS\' screen.</string>
    <string name="no_limit_warning">You must enter a maximum debt limit</string>
    <string name="no_savings">You haven\'t entered any savings yet.</string>
    <string name="no_spending_report">Warning: Once you delete this category, entries already made against it will no longer appear in the reports</string>
    <string name="no_spending_yet">You haven\'t entered any spending yet.</string>
    <string name="no_time">Click here if you don\'t have time to finish this right now.</string>
    <string name="no_time2">That\'s okay, just close the app and it will bring you right back here the next time you open it, or click on \"Done Entering Debts\" and you can finish this step later by going to DEBTS.</string>
    <string name="no_time3">That\'s okay, just close the app and it will bring you right back here the next time you open it, or click on \"Done Entering Savings\" and you can finish this step later by going to SAVINGS.</string>
    <string name="no_time4">That\'s okay, just close the app and it will bring you right back here the next time you open it, or click on \"Done Entering Budget\" and you can finish this step later by going to BUDGET.</string>
    <string name="not_enough_credit_warning">There is not enough credit available on this DEBTS item to make this transaction. You will be putting the debt over its limit.</string>
    <string name="not_enough_savings_warning">There is not enough in this SAVINGS item to make this transaction. You will be putting the savings balance into the negative.</string>
    <string name="not_now">not now</string>
    <string name="no_to_item_warning">You must choose an account to make the transfer to.</string>
    <string name="not_sure_yet">not sure yet</string>
    <string name="nov">November</string>
    <string name="oct">October</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="oops">Oops, you are spending more than you make!</string>
    <string name="on">charged on</string>
    <string name="on2">on</string>
    <string name="optional">This expense is optional (i.e. entertainment, gifts, clothing, etc)</string>
    <string name="outstanding_cc_purchases">Outstanding credit card purchases</string>
    <string name="over_limit">OVER LIMIT</string>
    <string name="own_account">Will this money be kept in your main bank account or separately, in its own account?</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="pay_cc">Pay credit cards</string>
    <string name="payments">Payments</string>
    <string name="pay_this_amount">Pay these amounts to your credit cards:</string>
    <string name="payment_not_possible_A">You don\'t have enough money in your account to make this purchase. You will put your balance into the negative.</string>
    <string name="payment_not_possible_B">You don\'t have enough spending money left in your account to make this purchase. You will be spending money that is reserved for other expenses.</string>
    <string name="percent" translatable="false">%</string>
    <string name="percent_sign">%</string>
    <string name="percent_spent">Percent Used</string>
    <string name="plus_button_debts">Press the PLUS button to add an item.</string>
    <string name="plus_button_savings">Press the PLUS button above to add savings.</string>
    <string name="previous">previous</string>
    <string name="purchases">Purchases</string>
    <string name="rate_it_question">Will you please take a moment to rate it?</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">Rate this app</string>
    <string name="record_cash_debit">Record another cash/debit</string>
    <string name="record_deposits">Record another deposit</string>
    <string name="record_money_in">Money going into main account</string>
    <string name="record_money_out">Cash or debit purchases</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="save_add_income">Save and add another income category</string>
    <string name="saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="savings">Savings</string>
    <string name="savings_1">Enter each of your savings and investment accounts as a separate SAVINGS account. They will automatically be added to your BUDGET as \"needs\" and the date that the savings goal will be achieved will be calculated for you.</string>
    <string name="savings_2">The app has calculated that the savings goal will not be achieved in a reasonable amount of time. Either the interest is too low or the contributions are too low or too infrequent.</string>
    <string name="savings_3">Simply click on the pencil icon next to the account in the SAVINGS screen and enter the new interest rate. A new \"goal achieved\" date will calculated.</string>
    <string name="savings_4">When you created the SAVINGS account, a linked income category was created for you in your BUDGET. Simply click on the pencil icon next to it on the BUDGET screen and enter the amount of income that you plan on taking from the SAVINGS account. A new \"goal achieved\" date will be calculated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="savings_5">Simply change the \"goal\" amount and a new \"goal achieved\" date will be calculated. Change the amount accordingly until the date is closest to your certain date.</string>
    <string name="savings_q1">I need guidance to enter savings accounts.</string>
    <string name="savings_q3">What if the interest rate changes in my SAVINGS account?</string>
    <string name="savings_q4">I frequently take cash withdrawals from a SAVINGS account, how should I get the app to handle this?</string>
    <string name="savings_q5">I don\'t have a particular financial goal I\'m trying to achieve, I want to know how much I\'ll accumulate by a certain date.</string>
    <string name="savings_saved">This savings info has been saved to your BUDGET</string>
    <string name="sep">September</string>
    <string name="separately">separately</string>
    <string name="set_up">Set Up</string>
    <string name="set_up_a1">Go to the DAILY MONEY - MONEY IN tab and click on the pencil icon next to the starting balance.</string>
    <string name="set_up_q1">How do I change the starting balance I entered during the set up process?</string>
    <string name="show">show</string>
    <string name="show_report">show report</string>
    <string name="skip_button">skip intro</string>
    <string name="sources_of_income">Sources of Income:</string>
    <string name="spending_report">Spending Report</string>
    <string name="spending_vs_earnings">Spending vs. Earnings</string>
    <string name="spent">Spent</string>
    <string name="start_button">Got it!</string>
    <string name="starting_balance">Starting Balance</string>
    <string name="starting_balance_amount">How much money is in your bank account today?</string>
    <string name="starting_balance_warning">*if you need to enter a negative number, some keyboards require you to push the decimal button twice in order to get a minus sign in front of your number</string>
    <string name="step_2">Step 2:</string>
    <string name="sure">sure!</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="to">to</string>
    <string name="too_far">Goal will not be achieved within your lifetime</string>
    <string name="total">Total:</string>
    <string name="total_budget">Total Budget</string>
    <string name="total_expenses">Total Expenses:</string>
    <string name="total_in_account">Total in account:</string>
    <string name="total_income">Total Income:</string>
    <string name="total_owing">Total Owing:</string>
    <string name="total_saved">Total Saved:</string>
    <string name="transfer_between">Transfers between accounts</string>
    <string name="transfer_complete">Amount transferred.</string>
    <string name="transfer_from">Transfer From:</string>
    <string name="transfer_funds">Transfer Funds</string>
    <string name="transfer_to">Transfer To:</string>
    <string name="undo_watch">undo watch</string>
    <string name="update">update</string>
    <string name="view_list">view list</string>
    <string name="view_weekly_limits">View weekly limits report</string>
    <string name="want_weekly_limits">Want MYnance to keep an eye on your weekly spending in certain areas?</string>
    <string name="warning">warning</string>
    <string name="watch_spending">watch</string>
    <string name="website" translatable="false">http://www.gotchasomething.ca</string>
    <string name="weekly">Weekly (52 times/yr)</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits">Weekly Limits</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_details">Mark expense items as \'optional\' and you\'ll then be asked whether or not you\'d like to track their spending on a weekly basis.</string>
    <string name="weekly_limit_exceeded">WEEKLY LIMIT EXCEEDED</string>
    <string name="weekly_limits_prompt">Weekly limits are set up in the VIEW/EDIT INCOME SOURCES/BILLS screen.</string>
    <string name="weekly_no">No: This is an occasional expense and I don\'t need weekly guidance</string>
    <string name="weekly_yes">Yes: I spend on this frequently and would like to be reminded of my limits</string>
    <string name="weekly_yes_or_no">Do you want this category added to the WEEKLY LIMITS tab to help you stay within your spending limits?</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_mynance">Welcome to MYnance!</string>
    <string name="what_to_do">What transactions do you want to enter?</string>
    <string name="which_debt">On which DEBT?</string>
    <string name="yearly">Once a year (1 time/yr)</string>
    <string name="year_to_date">Entire year to date</string>
    <string name="year_to_date1">all</string>
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="transactions">Transactions:</string>
    <string name="reports">Reports:</string>
    <string name="spending_summary">Spending Summary</string>
    <string name="create_transactions">Create transactions:</string>
    <string name="view_reports">View reports</string>
    <string name="inc_summary">Income Summary</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="Home_page">Home Page</string>
    <string name="edit_debts">View/Edit Debts</string>
    <string name="edit_savings">Savings</string>
    <string name="edit_incomes_bills">View/Edit Income/Expense Estimates</string>
    <string name="add_edit_weekly_limits">add/edit weekly limits</string>
    <string name="choose_year">Choose year:</string>
    <string name="record_credit_card">Record another credit card purchase</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="choose_card_and_amt">Choose a credit card and enter the amount of yiour payment</string>
    <string name="choose_month_year">Choose a month and year:</string>
    <string name="edit_credit_cards">Credit Cards/Lines of Credit</string>
    <string name="credit">Credit Cards/Lines of Credit:</string>
    <string name="another_credit">add another mode of credit</string>
    <string name="total_reserved">Total Reserved:</string>
    <string name="transfers">Transfers:</string>
    <string name="record_transfers">Record another transfer</string>
    <string name="edit_financial_summary">Financial Summary</string>
    <string name="reserved">Reserved:</string>
    <string name="reserved_includes">(Reserved funds are reserved for bills, other living expenses, and any default payment amounts to credit cards/lines of credit or savings accounts. Ideally, this should not be more than 80% of your income.)</string>
    <string name="i">i</string>
    <string name="make_adj">Make Adjustments:</string>
    <string name="credit_types">Credit Cards/Lines of Credit</string>
    <string name="another_expense">Add another expense</string>
    <string name="add_watch_or_create">Add or remove the weekly watching feature to categories below or CLICK HERE to create a new category that you want MYnance to watch for you.</string>
    <string name="new_cat">CLICK HERE to create a new category or choose one below</string>
    <string name="temp">temp</string>
    <string name="tempE">tempE</string>
    <string name="view_transactions">View/Edit Entries</string>
    <string name="credit_card_trans">Credit Card Transactions:</string>
    <string name="paid">Paid</string>
    <string name="debt_repay">Debt Repayment Plan</string>
    <string name="savings_plan">Savings Plan</string>
    <string name="money_in_out">Move money into or out of accounts:</string>
    <string name="take_control">Take control of your money:</string>
    <string name="choose_acct">Choose an account below</string>
    <string name="deposit_to">Deposit to:</string>
    <string name="money_from">Money from:</string>
    <string name="pay_from">Pay from:</string>
    <string name="spent_on">Spent on:</string>
    <string name="paid_from">paid from</string>
    <string name="main_account">Main Account</string>
    <string name="new_cc">CLICK HERE to create a new credit card or choose one below</string>
    <string name="deposited_to">deposited to</string>
    <string name="choose_split">How much should come from your reserved funds?</string>
    <string name="from_res">from reserved funds</string>
    <string name="from_avail">from available funds</string>
    <string name="all">all</string>
    <string name="none">none</string>
    <string name="split_as_follows">split as follows</string>
    <string name="split_as_usual">split as usual</string>
    <string name="custom_split">split as defined by me</string>
    <string name="not_enough">There is not enough money in your account</string>
    <string name="to_avail">to available funds</string>
    <string name="to_res">to reserved funds</string>
    <string name="same_acct">You must choose separate accounts</string>
    <string name="choose_split_inc">How much should go into your reserved funds?</string>
    <string name="reserved_for_bills">reserved for bills, etc.</string>
    <string name="weekly2">weekly</string>
    <string name="avail_for_bills">Available for paying bills, etc:</string>
    <string name="main_acct">Main Account</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="no_debts">You have no consumer debts!</string>
    <string name="you_have">You have</string>
    <string name="in_savings">in your savings.</string>
    <string name="towards_goal">of the way to your goal!</string>
    <string name="choose_type">Choose type of transaction:</string>
    <string name="cc_payts">Credit card payments</string>
    <string name="dialog">Warning: You will not be able to delete or edit credit card payment transactions.</string>
    <string name="credit_card_payts">Credit card payments:</string>
    <string name="paid_to">paid to</string>
    <string name="limit_list">Limit list to transactions between</string>
    <string name="and">and</string>
    <string name="no_entries">No entries in that date range</string>
    <string name="date_confusion">Your \"From\" date needs to be earlier than your \"To\" date</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="add_bill">Add a bill category</string>
    <string name="limit_report">Limit report to transactions between</string>
    <string name="choose_cat">Choose a category</string>
    <string name="total2">Total</string>
    <string name="inc_exp_report">Income and Expenses Report</string>
    <string name="over_weekly">This purchase will put you over your weekly limit in this category.</string>
    <string name="text">text</string>
    <string name="slide_image">slide image</string>
</resources>
